So how to prevent the elements of 2D array when we talk about arrays.
But 99 percent, the usage of loop.
OK, so I created a class multidimensional array and inside the main talking about Java code.
I have created an innate, multi-dimensional array, two brackets, angular brackets and called a and
I have put these elements one minus two or three minus four minus five, six, nine and seven.
In order to print all elements of 2D array, I need to go through and nested loop, so it's very important
to to understand this.
OK.
When we need to print an element in the elements of a one or single dimensional array, we have used
one loop.
But since we have to do two dimensional array, we need to use two nested loops.
The first one, it goes through that rows and the second one it will goes for the elements of the column.
So one for the rows, the first one for the rows, which is indexed by AI and iterated by AI.
And the second one is indexed and iterated through each of the elements of that column.
OK, now let's see how to use the for each loop.
There is another way of making this happens by insert by instantiating for each loop.
Despite using a nested loop.
If Index AI and Index J, we can use the same way in the previous slide.
The same way, but using the for each loop, the for each loop.
It is used when we have as an index and we have so we have elements.
We have specific elements and data structure.
We are not going to start from a specific position and to a specific position.
No, we are looping on each element in this data structure for this method, for this purpose.
It is named as for each loop, so it will look for each element in this data structure, so it will
start looping through all the elements, all the arrows.
It starts by four.
We specify and array in our array and we put a forward and data of in our array.
We print out that data so we are creating every time an element.
It's called data of type and it's inside the inner array and we are going to loop through all the elements
of this array.
And this way, this is the second way how to print the elements of a two dimensional array.
And in order to print the elements and add like in the classic way we use like this for nested loops.
OK.
Four.
And for loop and printing a at index I and the and index J.
OK.
At the Row I and Column J.
This is how we print all elements of data to the array using.
Two dimensional array uses.